ysearchtab.com 2017-06-03

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (the " **Policy** ") describes the privacy practices with respect to the service ("Services," as such term is defined in the end user license agreement available here: [support.ysearchtab.com/eula.html](http://support.ysearchtab.com/eula.html) (" **EULA** "). Please also review the EULA as your use of the Services are subject to the terms of this Policy and the EULA. 

By downloading and/or installing and/or using the Services and/or by accepting this Policy and the EULA, you also consent to the following privacy policy of Yahoo, whose products are offered to you as part of the Services (as explained in the EULA). We recommend that you review Yahoo's privacy policy which is available in the following link: <https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/search/details.html> (" **Third Party's Policies** "). 

By downloading and installing the Services and/or by accepting this Policy and the EULA, you consent to our access, collection, use and/or disclosure of your information as described in the Third Party's Policies and in this Policy. 

**1. _Information We Collect and Use_**

1.1 _Basic Information_. We may collect non-personal and technical information from you. This information may include your type of browser(s) and their homepage and default search, your IP address, device identifier and your computer operating system details. We collect and use this information to measure and improve the Software over time. We use the your browser's Local Storage and cockiest so we can store the details mentioned above locally within your browser for analytics, product enhancements, new development and to provide you with our Services. 

1.2 _Personal Information You Provide Us_. When you contact us, we keep a record of your communication with us (including your email address) ("Personal Information") to provide you with support services, and, if applicable, investigate any issues that you raise. We do not use this information for advertising purposes. 

**2. _Information Sharing and Disclosure_**

2.1. _General_. We do not rent, sell, or share your Personal Information except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or in the event that we have a good faith belief that disclosure is permitted by law or is reasonably necessary to: (i) comply with the law, a legal requirement or process, including without limitation, subpoenas, court orders, or other compulsory disclosures, or to establish, maintain or exercise our legal rights; (ii) enforce this Policy or the EULA; (iii) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or violation of third party rights; or (iv) protect our rights. In addition, in the event that we undergo a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be one of the assets sold or transferred. 

2.2. _Service Providers_. We may employ third parties to provide us with search feed, maintenance, analysis, audit, and development services with respect to the Software. We currently use (i) Yahoo - for search feed. You can read about Yahoo's privacy practice in the following link:<https://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/search/details.html>; (ii) Amazon Web Services, Inc. servers to store your data. You can read about the measures taken by Amazon to protect the security of their servers and your Personal Information at: <https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/>. 

2.3. _Corporate Affiliates_. We may also disclose your information to our corporate affiliates in order to help provide, understand, and improve the Services and our affiliates' services, this means we may also internally combine information we have on you. 

2.4. _Data Transfer_. We may transfer your information and process it on servers outside your country of residence. 

**3. _Security_**

We have implemented security safeguards designed to protect your Personal Information in accordance with industry standards. We limit access to your information on our servers, and it is password-protected/encrypted. We also regularly monitor our servers for possible vulnerabilities and attacks. Nevertheless, as the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us. There is no guarantee that information on our servers may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of our safeguards. 

**4. _Modifying Your Personal Information_**. 

You have a right to request that we delete any of your personal information in our possession by sending us an email to: [support@ysearchtab.com](mailto:support@ysearchtab.com) We will generally delete your information within 30 days of receipt of your request. 

**5. _Our Policy Towards Children_**

The Services is not intended and/or directed to persons under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under that age has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information from our servers. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [support@ysearchtab.com](mailto:support@ysearchtab.com). 

**6. _Changes to This Policy_**

We may change this Policy from time to time. If we make changes, that are significant in our sole discretion, in the way we treat your personal information, or to the Policy, we will provide you with notice as part of the Services or by any other means. Your continued use of the Services, following any change to this Policy, constitutes your complete and irrevocable acceptance of the updated Policy. If any changes to the Policy are not acceptable to you, you may uninstall the Services. 

**7. _Contact Information_**

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us at [support@ysearchtab.com](mailto:support@ysearchtab.com).
